<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agri Kissan Project</string>
    //navroop
    <string name="Profile1">Navroop Singh is a progressive farmer with extensive years of experience in the field of dairy farming. Particularly engaged in rearing the indigenous breed- Sahiwal naturally from last 8 years he has great skills and expertise in taking good production of milk from dairy farming. Currently, the number of cows in his dairy farm exceeds 100 and most of them are of Sahiwal breed which is considered to be the best breed in India. Adept in utilizing the natural resources and waste product of cows productively in the form of Jeev Amrit, Vermicompost, and Neem spray. With a previous track record of strong marketing skills, presently he is running his own milk brand in Rajasthan. Aims towards making people aware about best natural dairy farming tips and practices.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition1">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise1">Dairy Farming , Organic Fertilizers , Organic Farming , Soap Making</string>
    <string name="Qualification1">Engineer</string>

    //Gurpreet
    <string name="Profile2">Gurpreet Singh Shergill is working as a professional floriculturist in the farming field from past 20 years. Passion for cultivating flowers can be traced in his strong demonstrated history of floriculture where he has cultivated variety of horticulture crops. With the desire to pursue his lifetime career in floriculture he has developed his own brand- Shergill Farm Fresh which is famous in Punjab for its Rose Sharbat, Aloe Vera Juice and Amla Juice. Utilize his innovative skills in managing the natural resources and in developing machines to ease the farm work. One of his greatest invention is Gladiolus Bulb Grading Machine. Along with floriculture he is also involved in dairy farming, conventional agriculture, and vermin-culture practices. With his strong experience and expertise, he look towards upgrading the agriculture society by helping the farmers.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition2">Received Punjab Chief Minister Award by PAU, Ludhiana in 2011. Received Jagjivan Ram Innovative Farmer Award by ICAR, New Delhi in 2012. •	Received N.G. Ranga Farmer Award by ICAR, New Delhi in 2014. •	Received Innovative Farmer Award by IARI, New Delhi in 2015.</string>
    <string name="Expertise2">Floriculture, Fish Farming, Rose and Amla Juice</string>
    <string name="Qualification2">Diploma in Mechanical Engineering</string>
    //Harvinder
    <string name="Profile3">Harvinder is a Graduate in B.Sc. agriculture honors from Guru Kashi University. He has been actively involved in agriculture from childhood and helped his father and brother, where he gained good knowledge about traditional agriculture practices.. He has also worked with a private company and learned about organic farming, vermin compost and other organic farming practices. At the young age of 17 years he was nominated by the Indian Government to visit Japan to learn about the agricultural practices and lifestyle followed in Japan. Harvinder also spent a short span of his career working as an advisor with IFFCO (KCC) and is now associated with ApniKheti.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition3"> --- </string>
    <string name="Expertise3">Pest control and disease treatment Organic fertilizer Irrigation Crops and horticulture</string>
    <string name="Qualification3">B.Sc. Agriculture (Hons)</string>
    //Navdeep
    <string name="Profile4">Navdeep Singh Gill is among those knowledgeable farmers who have supported sustainable agriculture practices since he started farming. With his 30 years of experience in the field of farming he aims to look towards implementing eco-friendly farming technologies and utilizing natural resources cautiously to make earth a better place. Practicing natural farming from last 10 years, he has demonstrated a strong history of cultivating Cereals, Legumes, Oilseeds and Horticulture crops with great expertise. With his farming background and entrepreneurship quality, he is running his own brand – Thar Naturals, to sell his naturally harvested crops. Currently his main goal is to contribute his knowledge accumulated throughout his farming years to the farmer society and help them raise globally. For his tremendous contribution towards natural farming he is awarded with Krishak Samman Puraskar in 2016.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition4"> Receive Krishak Samman Puraskar, 2016 .Till now organized three Organic Prashikshan Seminar to help the farmers.</string>
    <string name="Expertise4">Organic Farming, Horticulture, Dairy Farming</string>
    <string name="Qualification4">B.com</string>
    //Ramandeep
    <string name="Profile5">Dr. Ramandeep Singh, Professor of Business Management, Punjab Agriculture University and his team are instrumental in promoting the concepts of Progressive Farming and Agri Business in Punjab through digital marketing and social media. Dr. Ramandeep Singh has been able to motivate farmers to pursue the challenging path of agri-preneurship. He and his team have guided the farmers to develop new products and concepts that have greater acceptability amongst the consumers, and in the process helped them to supplement their incomes and also forge linkages between the farmers, the agriculture supply chain and the consumers. These initiatives will contribute to the well being of the farming community and also enable them to adopt best global practices for entering the global markets.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition5">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise5">Marketing Management, Research Interests, Agri-business Management, Agri-marketing , Entrepreneurship Development</string>
    <string name="Qualification5">B.Sc.(Forestry), Punjab Agricultural University, Ludhiana (1986-91); MBA, Punjabi University, Patiala (1991-93); Ph.D.(Business Management); Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar, (2002-05)</string>
    //shilpa
    <string name="Profile6">Working as web content manager in ApniKheti. Me and my team, access and assimilate crop advisory content from trusted sources then create advisories through collected information. Along with content preparation, I am interested in to assist farmer on a number of areas, including cultivation, pest and disease management and harvesting. Agriculture is back bone of India and I want to work for well-being of Farmer.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition6">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise6">Pest and Disease Management, Cultivation, Fertilization, Harvesting</string>
    <string name="Qualification6">Master of Technology in Soil and Water Engineering</string>
    //hindpal
    <string name="Profile7">Trained in Jojoba Plantation and farming from Jaipur, Hind Pal Singh is one of the rising horticulturist from the land of Rajasthan. He is doing Jojoba farming from 12 years in 2 hectares of area and is generating good profit from it. He has guided many farmers of his area towards jojoba farming and will keep doing it in the future also. He use mechanized and modern ways for farming and marketing and that has made him expert in his work</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition7">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise7">Jojoba Farming</string>
    <string name="Qualification7">Bachelors in Hotel Management</string>
    //mittali
    <string name="Profile8">Mittali Sharma is an M.Sc. in Botany from Punjab University and has done her research work in Candium effects on Wheat. As a young research fellow she has expanded her research area from crops to livestock as well, covering total of 500 + crop varieties and 200 + animal breeds. She had been continuously following her passion of research on Agri Industry and regularly serving the cause dear to her heart, farming. Experience of 5 years in Botany Research Work- Cadmium effect on Wheat</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition8">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise8">Agriculture Research</string>
    <string name="Qualification8">M.Sc. in Botany, B.Sc. in Bioinformatics</string>
    //Rajmohan
    <string name="Profile9">Rajmohan Singh Kaleka is recognized as a role model in the peasant society of Punjab for his eco-friendly and poison less agriculture practices. For putting his effort from last 20 years in the field of pesticides free farming he is affiliated with terms like progressive farmer, scientist, officer and agricultural expert. Other than serving the agriculture field he also serves Rajeev Gandhi National University of Law (RGNUL, Punjab) as Liaison Officer. He is the first farmer from Punjab who has received Krishi Karman award for Prime Minister – Narendra Modi. One of the reasons that lead him to this level of accomplishment in his life is the advisories given by him to the agricultural experts, Punjab Agriculture University and IARI</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition9">Honoured by the Tutt Brothers at 4th Jat Expo Mela at Jalandhar on 09 November 2014. Honoured by Punjab Agriculture Department, Dist. Patiala, Young Farmer Rakhra, Director Agriculture Department Punjab and Joint Director IARI New Delhi Dr. K.V. Prabhu at Kissan Mela-cum-Farmer Training Camp on 27 September 2014. Honoured for saving soil, air and environment by the Tutt Brothers on 22 November 2014 at 5th Jat Expo Mela.Has been felicitated with State Award by the honourable Chief Minister of Punjab on 15th August 2015.Honoured by honourable Mr. Justice V. Gopal Gowda, Judge, and Supreme Court of India on 22 August 2015. Praised and honoured by the Governor of Punjab and Haryana, his Excellency Professor Kaptan Singh Solanki, at Kisan Mela Rakhra in collaboration with Punjab Agricultural Department on 16 September 2015. Honoured by Punjab Agriculture Department, Dist. Patiala, Young Farmer Rakhra, Chairman, Agriculture Scientist Recruitment Board New Delhi at Kisan Mela-cum-Farmer Training Camp on 12 March 2016. Has been selected to interact with Sh. Narinder ModiJi, Honourable Prime Minister of India and sensitize him over multiple issues pertaining to farming at the Inaugural Function of Krishi Unnati Mela-2016 on 19 March 2016. Honoured by the honourable Agriculture Minister of Punjab S. Tota Singh at Kisan Mela-cum- Farmer Training Camp Rakhra (Patiala) on 11.09.2016. Has been awarded with National Innovative Farmer Award-2016 by honourable Sh. Radha Mohan Singh, Union Agriculture Minister, Government of India, at National Agriculture fair 2016 KrishiUnnati, IARI New Delhi on 21 March 2016. Received Agriculture Minister Krishi Karman Award for Progressive Farmers-2017 and Prashasthi Patra by Honourable Sh. Narendra Modi Ji, Prime Minister of India on 17.03.2018 at New Delhi. Received Appreciation Letter from the Deputy Commissioner, Patiala and Chief Agriculture Officer, Patiala for ploughing the agriculture waste into the field on 11 April 2017.Honoured by the Honourable Smt. Preneet Kaur, Ex Minister of State in the Ministry of External Affairs on 17.07.2017 at fest organized by Markfed at Patiala. Honoured by the Honourable Rana K.P Singh, Speaker Punjab Vidhan Sabha, on 15.08.2017 at Patiala. Has been felicitated with District Award by the Honourable Speaker Punjab Vidhan Sabha on 15th August 2017. Honoured by Honourable Cabinet Minister, Punjab Shri Surjeet Singh Rakhra at Krishi Vigyan Kendar, Patiala. Appointed as Member of Agriculture Production Committee, District Patiala by Agriculture Department. Received Appreciation Letters from Honourable Agriculture Minister, Honourable Minister for Water Supply, Sanitation and Higher Education, Punjab, Chief Parliamentary Secretary (Agriculture) Punjab, Director of Agricultural Punjab, Joint Director (IARI) Delhi, and Deputy Commissioner Patiala. Honoured for chemical-free farming by Addl. Chief Secretary (Development) Punjab, Vice-Chancellor Punjab Agriculture University Ludhiana and Joint Director IARI New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="Expertise9">Rice, Wheat, Fruit and Vegetables</string>
    <string name="Qualification9">10+2</string>
    //Nishan
    <string name="Profile10">Nishandeep was doing private job as a teacher in Patti, Tarn Taran. But now he is doing organic farming for home. He grows crops are wheat, paddy, basmati, pea,moongi,mah,sarho, toriya, makki from last 7-8 years.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition10">---</string>
    <string name="Expertise10">Crops(wheat, paddy, basmati, pea,moongi,mah,sarho, toriya, makki)</string>
    <string name="Qualification10">B.A. and ETT</string>
    //Daljeet
    <string name="Profile11">Mr. Daljeet Singh has over 35 years of experience as a he was an Assistant Vegetable Botanist/Res.Asstt. (4.5.1974 to 31.08.1986), Senior Vegetable Botanist (1.1.1995 to 31.5.2002) Vegetable Botanist (1.9.1986 to 31.12.1994) and Senior Olericultrist (since 1.6.2002) at PAU. He was nominated as Member of the Vegetable Section of International Society of Horticultural Science (International Horticultural Congress in Japan 1994). He has attended Seven International Conferences. He has released several vegetable varieties like Pea Hara bona. – 1980, improved variety of lettuce Punjab Lettuce -1 – 1992 and bitter gourd Punjab-14 etc. and also recommended many technologies in agriculture.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition11">Selected for the Award of financial assistance amongst the outstanding pool of scientists representing the finest institutions in the country for attending International Conferences abroad by the Govt. of India, Deptt. of Sci. and Tech. (DST); Council of Scientific and Industrial Research (CSIR); Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR); World Vegetable Center (AVRDC) and Onion Association of Australia.Attended Seven International Conference at AVRDC, Taiwan, (1992), Univ. of Cuyo, Mendoza, Argentina (South America) in 1994 and Adelaide, Australia (1997) and New Delhi etc.Life Member of the Indian Society Vegetable Science, Varanasi.Nominated Member of the Chilli Exploration Team by the Project Directorate of Vegetable crops, Varanasi and Director NBPGR, New Delhi.Nominated Member of Vegetable Section (ISHS) by the Directors of International Society of Horticulture Science (One of the four members from India)Nominated Member of the Working Group of ISHS Water Supply and Irrigation (One of the three members from India).Member of the New York Academy of Sciences, New York.Member Indian Society of Plant Genetic Resources, New Delhi.Member Indian Society of Horticulture Science, New Delhi.Member Indian Society of Genetics and Plant Breeding, New Delhi.Life Member of Haryana Society of Horticulture Science, Hissar Participated in seminars/conferences/workshops.</string>
    <string name="Expertise11">Vegetable Breeder, Horticulture</string>
    <string name="Qualification11">Ph.D. (Olericulture), M.Sc. Horticulture) B.Sc. (Agriculture)</string>
    //Gurcharan
    <string name="Profile12">Gurcharan Singh Mann is a successful commercial apiculturist from Bathinda district of Punjab. After being trained in beekeeping under an advanced program of Punjab Agriculture University in 1990, he started with 7 bee boxes and today with the experience of 28 years he has expanded his beekeeping business to more than 1800 beehive boxes. By choosing the path of diversification today he has set up an empire- Mann Makhi Farm, where he is not only practicing beekeeping but also doing fish farming, nurturing sprawling orchards and cultivating vegetables. He has proved the right example of diversified farming by adopting different agri-allied activities and for his initiative he was also elected as the Best Farmer of the Year by Punjab Agriculture University. During his cumulative years he enhanced his knowledge by every possible way to achieve the expertise and skills for which he is popular today in the agriculture Society of Punjab. In future, he aims towards sharing his knowledge and experience with the budding farmers and help them grow.</string>
    <string name="AwardsandRecognition12">Gurcharan Singh Mann is a successful commercial apiculturist from Bathinda district of Punjab. After being trained in beekeeping under an advanced program of Punjab Agriculture University in 1990, he started with 7 bee boxes and today with the experience of 28 years he has expanded his beekeeping business to more than 1800 beehive boxes. By choosing the path of diversification today he has set up an empire- Mann Makhi Farm, where he is not only practicing beekeeping but also doing fish farming, nurturing sprawling orchards and cultivating vegetables. He has proved the right example of diversified farming by adopting different agri-allied activities and for his initiative he was also elected as the Best Farmer of the Year by Punjab Agriculture University. During his cumulative years he enhanced his knowledge by every possible way to achieve the expertise and skills for which he is popular today in the agriculture Society of Punjab. In future, he aims towards sharing his knowledge and experience with the budding farmers and help them grow.</string>
    <string name="Expertise12">Beekeeping, Floriculture, Fishery</string>
    <string name="Qualification12">B.A.</string>


</resources>
